cashtrafic.com 2014-06-30

# Adcash® Advertising Network | International Advertising Platform

Overview  
At **Adcash** ® we are deeply committed to respect and protect the privacy of our online visitors.  
Our privacy policy governs the way in which we use and disclose any personal information we may learn about you when you visit our website [www.adcash.com](https://www.adcash.com/) (“Site”).  
In addition to our Privacy Policy, the Site is governed by a terms and conditions agreement ([www.adcash.com/terms.php](https://www.adcash.com/terms.php)), which governs in the event of any conflict with this Privacy Policy. By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy.  
The Policy is not exhaustive and Adcash.com reserves the right to add, delete, or modify any provision of the Policy at any time without notice to yourself, effective upon the posting of the modified Policy to [www.adcash.com](https://www.adcash.com/). Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.  
  
Information Collection, Use and Disclosure  
**Adcash** ® adheres to the privacy guidelines created by the Interactive Advertising Bureau (IAB) and Direct Marketing Association (DMA). We not collect any personally identifiable information (PII) from visitors.

**Adcash** ® is an advertising platform. When you see an ad that has been served by **Adcash.com** , the website you are visiting has commissioned **Adcash** ® to act as an agent to deliver advertisements and report on advertising activity. The website you are visiting may be an **Adcash** ® customer or a website who is selling ad space to one of **Adcash** ®'s customers.

**Adcash** ®, through the use of cookies and pixel tags, collects anonymous usage statistics. These are industry standard technologies used by many major websites. No personally identifiable information is collected or used in this process. Information that is collected may include: session data, geography, browser information, IP address, operating system type.

**Adcash** ® does not provide any of your personal information to our customer or their partners when you view an ad. The data we collect using cookies and pixel tags is only viewable by our customers and contains no personally identifiable information.

Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act) and do not knowingly collect information from anyone under the age of 13 years. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

Cookie Usage  
Like most Internet sites, **Adcash.com** may use cookies to enhance user’s browsing experience and prevent them from seeing the same advertisements repeatedly. These cookies are not used to personally identify you in any way, nor will they damage your system or files.  
Cookies are small files that a site transfers to your computer's hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.  
Cookies can also be used for Pixel tracking which is explained below.

It is possible to tell your browser to reject cookies for all sites or specific sites. Rejecting cookies is not recommended however, as cookies are intended to improve your browsing experience. For more information about removing cookies, please see the "Opting Out" section below.

Pixel Tracking  
To ensure the correct delivery and effectiveness of our customer's advertising campaigns, we use pixel tracking tags to measure usage statistics.  
**Adcash** ®’s customers can place pixel tags on their partner websites. These tags allow our software to measure non-personal behavioral patterns to indicate the effectiveness of the advertising. No personally identifiable information is collected during this process.

Audience Pixels  
In order to ensure that users are getting the best level of advertising, **Adcash** ® uses audience pixels to match ads to users. Audience pixels do not store any personally identifiable information.  
We use audience pixels to match advertisements that may be of interest to our users or to assist our advertisers, ad networks, carriers and publisher web sites to deliver advertisements and offers that may be of interest to users within a given segment.  
The activity information collected during this process is not used in any other way by **Adcash** ® or its clients other than to serve advertisements.  
If you would like to opt-out of **Adcash** ®'s audience pixel technology please see instructions below in the "Opting Out" section.  
  
Opting Out  
To avoid storing information in your browser, you can easily deny, or opt out of, cookies either by:  
a) manually deleting them (follow the instructions contained in the "Help" section of your browser);  
b) choosing to [permanently opt-out by clicking here](https://www.adcash.com/privacy.php?optout=0) from seeing advertisements matching your interests.  
In order to opt-out, you must have cookies enabled. If you use a different computer, change web browsers or delete this cookie, you will need to repeat the process. If you wish to see ads tailored for you, please [opt-in again](https://www.adcash.com/privacy.php?optout=1).

Terms and Conditions  
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [www.adcash.com/terms.php](https://www.adcash.com/terms.php)

Contact Us  
If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the practices of this site, you can contact us via: [contact@adcash.com](mailto:contact@adcash.com) or write to us using contact form [here](https://www.adcash.com/contact.php)

**Adcash OÜ**  
Kentmanni 4  
10116 Tallinn, Estonia   
Email: [legal@adcash.com](mailto:legal@adcash.com)
